var data = [
	{"id":0, "name": "harrypotter0", "answer": {"a": "Hagrid", "b": "Albus Dumbledore", "c": "Mr. Weasley", "d": "Hermione Granger"}, "question": "You're a wizard Harry", "correct_answer": "Hagrid"},
	{"id":1, "name": "harrypotter1", "answer": {"a": "Remus Lupin", "b": "Albus Dumbledore", "c": "Serius Snape", "d": "Mr. Weasley"}, "question": "But you know, happiness can be found even in the darkest of times, if one only remembers to turn on the light", "correct_answer": "Albus Dumbledore"},
	{"id":2, "name": "harrypotter2", "answer": {"a": "Albus Dumbledore", "b": "Severus Snape", "c": "Hermione Granger", "d": "Ron Weasley"}, "question": "We could all have been killed --or worse, expelled", "correct_answer": "Hermione Granger"},
	{"id":3, "name": "harrypotter3", "answer": {"a": "Mr. Weasley", "b": "Hagrid", "c": "Albus Dumbledore", "d": "Remus Lupin"}, "question": "Never trust anything that can think for itself if you can't see where it keeps its brain", "correct_answer": "Mr. Weasley"},
	{"id":4, "name": "harrypotter4", "answer": {"a": "Albus Dumbledore", "b": "Severus Snape", "c": "Ron Weasley", "d": "Harry Potter"}, "question": "Always", "correct_answer": "Severus Snape"},

	{"id":5, "name": "perks0", "answer": {"a": "Sam", "b": "Charlie", "c": "Bill (teacher)", "d": "Patrick"}, "question": "We accept the love we think we deserve", "correct_answer": "Bill (teacher)"},
	{"id":6, "name": "perks1", "answer": {"a": "Sam", "b": "Charlie", "c": "Bill (teacher)", "d": "Patrick"}, "question": "So, this is my life. And I want you to know that I am both happy and sad and I'm still trying to figure out how that could be.", "correct_answer": "Charlie"},
	{"id":7, "name": "perks2", "answer": {"a": "Sam", "b": "Charlie", "c": "Bill (teacher)", "d": "Patrick"}, "question": "Why do I and everyone I love pick people who treat us like we're nothing?", "correct_answer": "Sam"},
	{"id":8, "name": "perks3", "answer": {"a": "Sam", "b": "Charlie", "c": "Bill (teacher)", "d": "Patrick"}, "question": "Hey, everyone! Every body! Everyone, raise your glasses to Charlie.", "correct_answer": "Patrick"},
	{"id":9, "name": "perks4", "answer": {"a": "Sam", "b": "Charlie", "c": "Bill (teacher)", "d": "Patrick"}, "question": "Dear Friend, I'm sorry I haven't written in a while, but I've been trying hard not to be a loser.", "correct_answer": "Charlie"},

	{"id":10, "name": "thecircle0", "answer": {"a": "Eamon Bailey", "b": "Mae", "c": "Mercer", "d": "Annie"}, "question": "Better to be at the bottom of a ladder you want to climb than in the middle of some ladder you don’t, right?", "correct_answer": "Annie"},
	{"id":11, "name": "thecircle1", "answer": {"a": "Eamon Bailey", "b": "Mercer", "c": "Mae", "d": "Francis"}, "question": "It’s not that I’m not social. I’m social enough. But the tools you guys create actually manufacture unnaturally extreme social needs.", "correct_answer": "Mercer"},
	{"id":12, "name": "thecircle2", "answer": {"a": "Annie", "b": "Mae", "c": "Mercer", "d": "Eamon Bailey"}, "question": "In a world where bad choices are no longer an option, we have no choice but to be good.", "correct_answer": "Eamon Bailey"},
	{"id":13, "name": "thecircle3", "answer": {"a": "Francis", "b": "Mae", "c": "Mercer", "d": "Annie"}, "question": "Every time my brain parks the car neatly in the driveway, my mouth drives through the back of the garage", "correct_answer": "Francis"},
	{"id":14, "name": "thecircle4", "answer": {"a": "Mae", "b": "Eamon Bailey", "c": "Mercer", "d": "Annie"}, "question": "It was not knowing that was the seed of madness, loneliness, suspicion, fear.", "correct_answer": "Mae"},

	{"id":15, "name": "friends0", "answer": {"a": "Monica Geller", "b": "Rachel Green", "c": "Phoebe Buffay", "d": "Janice Litman"},  "question": "Oh my God.", "correct_answer": "Janice Litman"},
	{"id":16, "name": "friends1", "answer": {"a": "Ross Geller", "b": "Chandler Bing", "c": "Joey Tribbiani", "d": "Phoebe Buffay"}, "question": "How you doin?", "correct_answer": "Joey Tribbiani"},
	{"id":17, "name": "friends2", "answer": {"a": "Chandler Bing", "b": "Rachel Green", "c": "Joey Tribbiani", "d": "Janice Litman"}, "question": " I'm not so good with the advice... Can I interest you in a sarcastic comment?", "correct_answer": "Chandler Bing"},
	{"id":18, "name": "friends3", "answer": {"a": "Ross Geller", "b": "Rachel Green", "c": "Chandler Bing", "d": "Monica Geller"}, "question": "We were on a break!", "correct_answer": "Ross Geller"},
	{"id":19, "name": "friends4", "answer": {"a": "Ross Geller", "b": "Rachel Green", "c": "Phoebe Buffay", "d": "Monica Geller"}, "question": "I got off the plane", "correct_answer": "Rachel Green"},

	{"id":20, "name": "wizardofoz0", "answer": {"a": "The Wizard of Oz", "b": "Dorthy", "c": "The Lion", "d": "The Scarecrow"}, "question": "There's no place like home.", "correct_answer": "Dorthy"},
	{"id":21, "name": "wizardofoz1", "answer": {"a": "The Wizard of Oz", "b": "Glinda the Good Witch", "c": "The Lion", "d": "The Wicked Witch of the West"}, "question": "I'll get you, my pretty, and your little dog too!", "correct_answer": "The Wicked Witch of the West"},
	{"id":22, "name": "wizardofoz2", "answer": {"a": "The Wizard of Oz", "b": "The Tinman", "c": "The Lion", "d": "The Scarecrow"},  "question": "You're right, I am a coward! I haven't any courage at all. I even scare myself.", "correct_answer": "THe Lion"},
	{"id":23, "name": "wizardofoz3", "answer": {"a": "The Wizard of Oz", "b": "The Tinman", "c": "The Lion", "d": "The Scarecrow"},  "question": "Frightened? Child, you're talking to a man who's laughed in the face of death, sneered at doom, and chuckled at catastrophe. I was petrified", "correct_answer": "The Wizard of Oz"},
	{"id":24, "name": "wizardofoz4", "answer": {"a": "The Wizard of Oz", "b": "The Tinman", "c": "The Lion", "d": "The Scarecrow"},  "question": "I don't know, but some people without brains do an awful lot of talking,don't they?", "correct_answer": "The Scarecrow"},

	{"id":25, "name": "lost0", "question": "See you in another life brotha.", "answer": {"a": "Desmond Hume", "b": "John Locke", "c": "Hurley Garcia", "d": "Charlie Pace"}, "correct_answer": "Desmond Hume"},
	{"id":26, "name": "lost1", "question": "Don't tell me what I can't do!", "answer": {"a": "Desmond Hume", "b": "John Locke", "c": "Hurley Garcia", "d": "Charlie Pace"}, "correct_answer": "John Locke"},
	{"id":27, "name": "lost2", "question": "Guys....where Are we?", "answer": {"a": "Desmond Hume", "b": "John Locke", "c": "Hurley Garcia", "d": "Charlie Pace"}, "correct_answer": "Charlie Pace"},
	{"id":28, "name": "lost3", "question": "DUDE!", "answer": {"a": "Desmond Hume", "b": "John Locke", "c": "Hurley Garcia", "d": "Charlie Pace"}, "correct_answer": "Hurley Garcia"},
	{"id":29, "name": "lost4", "question": "Kate, we have to go back.", "answer": {"a": "James Ford", "b": "Jack Shepherd", "c": "Hurley Garcia", "d": "Charlie Pace"}, "correct_answer": "Jack Shepherd"},

	{"id":30, "name": "arresteddevelopment0", "answer": {"a": "Buster Bluth", "b": "Lucille Bluth", "c": "Michael Bluth", "d": "Gob Bluth"}, "question": "I've made a huge mistake?", "correct_answer": "Gob Bluth"},
	{"id":31, "name": "arresteddevelopment1", "answer": {"a": "Michael Bluth", "b": "Lucille Bluth", "c": "Gob Bluth", "d": "Tobias Funke"}, "question": "I don't know what I expected.", "correct_answer": "Michael Bluth"},
	{"id":32, "name": "arresteddevelopment2", "answer": {"a": "Tobias Funke", "b": "Michael Bluth", "c": "Tobias Funke", "d": "Lucille Bluth"}, "question": "I don't understand the question and I won't respond to it.", "correct_answer": "Lucille Bluth"},
	{"id":33, "name": "arresteddevelopment3", "answer": {"a": "Michael Bluth", "b": "John Locke", "c": "Buster Bluth", "d": "Gob Bluth"}, "question": "I'm a monster", "correct_answer": "Buster Bluth"},
	{"id":34, "name": "arresteddevelopment4", "answer": {"a": "Lucille Bluth", "b": "Tobias Funke", "c": "George Sr. Bluth", "d": "Gob Bluth"}, "question": "There was money in that banana stand.", "correct_answer": "George Sr. Bluth"},

	{"id":35, "name": "theoffice0", "answer": {"a": "Michael", "b": "Stanley", "c": "Creed", "d": "Dwight"}, "question": "There's too many people on this earth. We need a new plague", "correct_answer": "Dwight"},
	{"id":36, "name": "theoffice1", "answer": {"a": "Michael", "b": "Jim", "c": "Michael", "d": "Dwight"}, "question": "Just pretend like we're talking until the cops leave", "correct_answer": "Creed"},
	{"id":37, "name": "theoffice2", "answer": {"a": "Michael", "b": "Creed", "c": "Meredith", "d": "Dwight"}, "question": "The worse thing about prison was--was the Dementors", "correct_answer": "Michael"},
	{"id":38, "name": "theoffice3", "answer": {"a": "Michael", "b": "Stanley", "c": "Pam", "d": "Dwight"}, "question": "Did I stutter?", "correct_answer": "Stanley"},
	{"id":39, "name": "theoffice4", "answer": {"a": "Michael", "b": "Jim", "c": "Pam", "d": "Andy"}, "question": "He said, 'If I'm dead, you guys have been dead for weeks.''", "correct_answer": "Pam"},
]
export default data;
